<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<igre>

    <igra>
      <slikaIgre>Slike/Igre/BF1</slikaIgre>
      <naslovIgre> Battlefied 1 </naslovIgre>
      <opisIgre>
        Fight your way through epic battles ranging from tight urban combat in a besieged French
        city to the heavily defended mountain forts in the Italian Alps, or frantic combats in the deserts of Arabia.
        Discover a world at war through an adventure-filled campaign, or join in epic multiplayer battles
        with up to 64 players, and adapt your tactics to the earth-shattering destruction and dynamic weather.
        Fight as infantry, lead horse charges or take control of amazing vehicles on land, air and sea,
        from tanks and biplanes to the gigantic Behemoths – some of the largest vehicles in Battlefield history.
      </opisIgre>
      <cijenaIgre>60KM</cijenaIgre>
    </igra>

    <igra>
      <slikaIgre>Slike/Igre/TitanFall</slikaIgre>
      <naslovIgre>Titanfall 2</naslovIgre>
      <opisIgre>
        Bigger weapons make better friends in Titanfall 2, the epic follow-up to the genre-redefining Titanfall.
        Respawn Entertainment gives you the most advanced titan technology in its new, expansive single player
        campaign and multiplayer experience. Combine and conquer with new titans and pilots, deadlier weapons, and
        feature-rich customization and progression system that helps you and your titan flow as one unstoppable killing
        force. Unite and destroy. Become One.
      </opisIgre>
      <cijenaIgre>60KM</cijenaIgre>
    </igra>

    <igra>
        <slikaIgre>Slike/Igre/FFXV</slikaIgre>
        <naslovIgre> Fintal fantasy XV </naslovIgre>
        <opisIgre>
          Enter the world of FINAL FANTASY XV, and experience epic action-packed battles along your journey of discovery.
          You are Noctis, the Crown Prince of the Kingdom of Lucis, and your quest is to reclaim your homeland from
          the clutches of the imperial army.

          Joined by your closest friends, you will take the wheel and experience a voyage like no
          other, travelling through the breathtaking world of Eos encountering larger-than-life
           beasts and unforgiving enemies. You will learn to master the skills of weaponry
           and magic, channelling the power of your ancestors allowing you to effortlessly warp through the
           air in thrilling combat.
        </opisIgre>
        <cijenaIgre>60KM</cijenaIgre>
      </igra>

      <igra>
          <slikaIgre>Slike/Igre/GothicArmada</slikaIgre>
          <naslovIgre>Gothic Armada  </naslovIgre>
          <opisIgre>
            Battlefleet Gothic: Armada is the RTS videogame adaptation of Games Workshop’s classic tabletop
            game, pitting the Chaos, Imperium, Eldar, and Orks against each other in visceral space-battles.

            Developed with Unreal Engine 4, Battlefleet Gothic: Armada offers deep management of every ship
            composing the player’s fleet, both during and between battles. From the fastest frigates to the
            gigantic, miles-long battleships, the player will customize all aspects of his
            ships: weaponry, defense and support sub-systems, but also crew, captains, and more... each
            customization affecting the very performances of the ship and the special abilities available during
            battle. From battle to battle, the admirals and crew of surviving ships will gain
            experience and promotions, improving the battle-readiness of the ships for future, bigger and more
            dangerous battles.
          </opisIgre>
          <cijenaIgre>60KM</cijenaIgre>
        </igra>

</igre>
